CARD GAMES [Canasta](https://cardgames.io/canasta/) [Crazy Eights](https://cardgames.io/crazyeights/) [Cribbage](https://cardgames.io/cribbage/) [Euchre](https://cardgames.io/euchre/) [Gin Rummy](https://cardgames.io/ginrummy/) [Go Fish](https://cardgames.io/gofish/) [Hearts](https://cardgames.io/hearts/) [Idiot](https://cardgames.io/idiot/) [Lockup](https://cardgames.io/lockup/) [Manni](https://cardgames.io/manni/) [Oh Hell!](https://cardgames.io/ohhell/) [Pinochle](https://cardgames.io/pinochle/) [Rummy](https://cardgames.io/rummy/) [Spades](https://cardgames.io/spades/) [Spit](https://cardgames.io/spit/) [Switch](https://cardgames.io/switch/) [Thirteen](https://cardgames.io/thirteen/) [War](https://cardgames.io/war/) [Whist](https://cardgames.io/whist/)

SOLITAIRES [Addiction](https://cardgames.io/addiction/) [Canfield Solitaire](https://cardgames.io/canfieldsolitaire/) [Clock Solitaire](https://cardgames.io/clocksolitaire/) [Crescent Solitaire](https://cardgames.io/crescentsolitaire/) [FreeCell](https://cardgames.io/freecell/) [Golf Solitaire](https://cardgames.io/golfsolitaire/) [Kings in the Corners](https://cardgames.io/kingsinthecorners/) [Pyramid Solitaire](https://cardgames.io/pyramidsolitaire/) [Scorpion Solitaire](https://cardgames.io/scorpionsolitaire/) [Solitaire](https://cardgames.io/solitaire/) [Spider Solitaire](https://cardgames.io/spidersolitaire/) [Tri Peaks Solitaire](https://cardgames.io/tripeakssolitaire/) [Yukon Solitaire](https://cardgames.io/yukonsolitaire/)

OTHER GAMES [Backgammon](https://cardgames.io/backgammon/) [Checkers](https://cardgames.io/checkers/) [Chess](https://cardgames.io/chess/) [Farkle](https://cardgames.io/farkle/) [Mahjong](https://cardgames.io/mahjong/) [Minesweeper](https://cardgames.io/minesweeper/) [Reversi](https://cardgames.io/reversi/) [Sea Battle](https://cardgames.io/seabattle/) [Sudoku](https://cardgames.io/sudoku/) [Triangles](https://cardgames.io/triangles/) [Yahtzee](https://cardgames.io/yahtzee/)

Change language [ENGLISH](https://cardgames.io/privacy/) [ESPAÑOL](https://cardgames.io/es/privacy/) [FRANÇAIS](https://cardgames.io/fr/privacy/) [ÍSLENSKA](https://cardgames.io/is/privacy/)

Random game

OUR OTHER SITES [SPACEBUGS.IO](https://spacebugs.io/) [SUDOKU.LOL](https://sudoku.lol/)

CLOSE GAME MENU [Customize...](#customize-menu) [Hide 'Home' link](#hide-home)

Advertisement

🌎 English Español Français Íslenska

PRIVACY POLICY
==============

Advertisement

This site, [CardGames.io](https://cardgames.io/), is created by Rauðás Games ehf ("RedAce Games LLC"), a small software company in Iceland. Here we will explain what data we store and for what purpose, how we store it, how we use cookies and related technologies and how our advertising works. You can also [manage your cookie settings](#settings).

### Personal information

We do not store on our servers any personally identifiable data about users, such as name, location, playing habits or anything else. We have no user accounts so we simply don't have that kind of information available to us, nor do we want it.

If you email us for support we will have your email address and name in our mailbox. The email address is never used for any purpose other than to reply to your support requests and is never shared with any third parties. The same applies if you send us a message via social media or contact us via any method that reveals personal information about you to us: any information you reveal to us about yourself will only be stored and processed as needed to respond to your request.

Occationally we ask people more specific information about their devices when we are troubleshooting, such as what hardware they use, what browser they are playing the site on, details on their operating system of choice, or other technical data that could be used to identify that person. Aside from using that data to help us figure out your problem we do not collect, process, or otherwise store that data beyond what we need to help you, and we do not share any data with third parties.

### Aggregate data and statistics

We collect data about gameplay in the form of aggregated events, for example how much the computer player wins, how many games were played each day, errors that the code may report during operation, and other metrics about the games. This data is stored in a database on our servers. It is not tied to individual users, we simply collect it as for example "There were 30.000 games of Hearts played today", with nothing tying that back to who played those 30.000 games. The purpose of this data is to improve the games and adjust the computer players difficulty.

### Log Files

We keep log files of visits to the site. These log files include information about your IP address, the time of your visit, which page was visited and what type of browser was used.

### Cookies & related technologies

We use cookies (small bits of information stored on your computer), and other related technologies such as [Local Storage](http://www.w3.org/TR/webstorage/) for a few things:

* To remember which options you have chosen for the games.
* To remember the score between rounds in the games, who was the dealer and other game specific information.
* To keep statistics about your success in the games. These statistics are only stored in your browser, we don't store them on servers anywhere. You can always delete this data by going to your browser settings and clearing out all data from this website.
* To help us count the number of visitors to our website, i.e. a cookie is used so that you are not counted as 20 visitors if you play 20 games in one day.
* We use a cookie to store information about your consent of our cookie use.

The use of cookies listed above is by us, CardGames.io, and is necessary for the website to function properly. These are called 1st party cookies, because they are set and read only by us, not by any third parties. If you do not accept these cookies, either by not agreeing to the cookie consent form (for instance if you're in the EU/EEA) or by disabling cookies in your browser, then you will not be able to play the games normally. Below you can read about 3rd party cookies that are used for advertising.

### Google Analytics

In addition to aggregate data collected by us as described above, this website utilizes Google Analytics for additional insights in to how our users use our website and how we can improve it. This data is collected in aggregate and stored on Google servers. We use Google analytics to measure how many people visit us, how many people play each of our games, how much time people spend on our site, how many people visit from each country, what browsers are being used, and other more broken-down diagnosic data than what we collect on our own servers.

Google may utilize personal information in forming the aggregate data, but by the time we get access to the data all personally identifiable information has been stripped away: much like with data we collect ourselves we are able to use Google Analytics to see that 4000 people using Google Chrome visited our site and that on average they spent 20 minutes playing games, but we cannot trace that back to any specific user - all data we are interested in is collected in aggregate and we configure Google Analytics to store as little data about our users as possible. We will never know what browser you specifically use, what you do on our page, where you live, or anything else that specifically allows us to identify you based on your data.

Where GDPR applies users will be prompted to accept our use of Google Analytics the first time they visit the site. Regardless of where you live, if you do not agree with our use of Google Analytics you can toggle it below. This will prevent any GA scripts from being loaded, and thus prevents data being transmitted to Google servers.

Google Analytics cookies are categorized as **"Performance Cookies"**. Opting out of that category will disable Google Analytics.

### Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

We use Freestar, Google adsense, and other advertising providers to source and serve ads on our site. These ad companies will set cookies in your browser and read existing cookies that they have set before, possibly during visits to other sites. These are called 3rd party cookies, since they are from entities other than CardGames.io. These ad companies use this to serve you personalized ads, e.g. if you have been looking at shoes on a shopping site you might see ads for shoes here on cardgames.io. Below is the full list of ad companies which might set or read cookies in your browser during your use of CardGames.io, and a link to each company's privacy policy where they detail how they handle your data and what data they use to serve you ads.

#### Ad companies

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Freestar | [Privacy statement](https://freestar.com/privacy-policy/) |
| Google | [Privacy statement](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/) |
| Criteo | [Privacy statement](https://www.criteo.com/privacy/) |
| Adobe Advertising Cloud | [Privacy statement](https://www.adobe.com/privacy/general-data-protection-regulation.html) |
| Amazon | [Privacy statement](https://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=201909010) |
| AppLovin Corp. | [Privacy statement](https://www.applovin.com/privacy) |
| AppNexus | [Privacy statement](https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy) |
| Dentsu Aegis Network | [Privacy statement](http://www.dentsu.com/termsofuse/data_policy.html) |
| eBay | [Privacy statement](https://www.ebay.com/help/policies/member-behaviour-policies/user-privacy-notice-privacy-policy?id=4260#section12) |
| Facebook | [Privacy statement](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update) |
| Interpublic Group | [Privacy statement](https://www.interpublic.com/privacy-notice) |

Cookies these companies set during your visit here may be used to serve you targeted ads on other sites you visit later. Users in the EU or EEA will have to explicitly accept cookie use before any cookies are set in their browser. For users outside the EU/EEA, for example users in the USA, cookies will be allowed by default except where otherwise specified by law. Anyone, both in the EU/EEA and outside it, is free to opt out of the use of personalized ads below. You will still be shown ads, but the ad companies will not use cookies to tie you to other data and show you personalized ads. The ads you see if you opt out will be less relevant for you. Even if you opt out of personalized ads, the ad companies will still use cookies for purposes like making sure you are not shown the same ad over and over again, but this cookie will not be tied to any other data about you.

Advertising cookies are categorized as **"Targeting Cookies"**. Opting out of that category will not disable adverts, but will prevent them from setting cookies and thus making them serve generic ads instead.

If you have configured your browser to send the [Do-not-track](https://allaboutdnt.com/) header then we will always request non-personalized ads for you, no matter what you have chosen here on the site.

For a better explanation of exactly what Google does with your data, please visit [https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites) where they explain it in detail. You can also visit [https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) where they talk specifically about ads and cookie use related to it, and you can opt out of personalized advertising from Google across all sites.

This Site is primarily affiliated with Publisher First, Inc. dba Freestar ("Freestar") for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and Freestar will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about Freestar's data usage, [Click here](https://freestar.com/privacy-policy/)

#### List of third party cookies

While we cannot predict ahead of time which cookies third parties might set, our consent provider regularily scans our site and takes note of any cookies set. You can review the list of cookies found to date by clicking the button below

Show cookie list

Close

### Your privacy settings

Due to your detected location, consent is implied. You must explicitly opt out of non-essential cookies.

A choice was last made on our cookie policy on . You have allowed us to set **all cookies**. cookies, but rejected cookies. You can alter your consent by pressing the button below.

You have not accepted our cookie policy yet. By default we assume you've rejected all non-essential cookies until you've granted consent. You can configure your consent by pressing the button below.

Cookie Settings

### Contact us

If you would like more information about any of the above, please do not hesitate to contact us at [support@cardgames.io](mailto:support@cardgames.io) with any questions or concerns.

Click here to go back to the frontpage.

This is version 1.23.5 of CardGames.io.

Game failed to load
-------------------

The primary script that runs our games seems to not have loaded, somehow.

This is in despite of the fact other scripts seem to have loaded up just fine.

This issue has been automatically reported and we're looking into it, but we'd be very grateful if you could send a report to [support@cardgames.io](mailto:support@cardgames.io) with any further detail you can think of, including if you're running any script-blocking extensions, ad-blockers, or if your browser is set to block specific types of scripts.

You have Javascript disabled!
-----------------------------

We detected that something blocked cardgames.io from running Javascript files on the page. Unfortunately, all the games are coded in Javascript, and so our site cannot function without executing scripts.

Please either enable Javascript for Cardgames.io from your brower's security settings, or upgrade to a more modern browser.

If you've found that your browser is executing scripts on other sites and cardgames.io isn't being blocked by any settings, extensions, or other add-ons you have running on your computer send a detailed report to [support@cardgames.io](mailto:support@cardgames.io)
